Seth Tal

Email: Seth.tal255@gmail.com, Cell: (408) 688-1255, Current Address: 1727 Mill St. #2, Eugene, OR, 97401

Professional Summary ~ Full Time Student

Just completed my Sophomore year at the University of Oregon and will begin my Junior year starting in October 2019. Attempting to Major in Computer Information Technology (CIS) with an avid passion for programming and video game development. Acquired job experience in three different positions at three separate establishments. The experiences gained from each position include but are not limited to cleaning and maintaining a facility, prepping food, customer service, front desk work, and the ability to develop strong work relations with peers.

Work History

Restaurant Team Member ~ 06/2017 to 09/2017

Chipotle - Los Gatos, CA

Collaborated with multiple individuals preparing food, cleaning and maintaining the facility, and assisting customers when needed.

- Learned about the inner workings of culinary establishments
- Gained insight on positive customer service practices
- · Improved ability to work efficiently under pressure

Front Desk Staff ~ 06/2017 to 09/2017

The Club at Los Gatos - Los Gatos, CA

Spent long hours looking after the needs of multiple customers and maintaining the facility. Developed close interpersonal work relations with multiple staff.

- Acquired knowledge of proper cleaning practices when looking after a facility
- Collaborated closely with peers, and developed multiple friendships
- Gained insight on improving work ethic

Delivery Driver ~ 08/2018 to 08/2019

DoorDash - Los Gatos, CA

Worked full-time over the summer delivering meals to customers from a variety of store locations, while having to deal with a variety of customers.

- Developed ability to be responsible and communicative in a work environment
- Gained strong sense of integrity
- Acquired a strong sense of identity

Education

Los Gatos High School ~ Attended for 4 yrs.

Graduated

GPA: (cumulative) 3.0

University of Oregon ~ Attended for 2 yrs.

Still Attending

GPA: (prev term) 3.5, (cumulative) 3.0

Links

GitHub: https://github.com/Sephta - username: Sephta

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/seth-tal-98883a18b/ - user: Seth Tal

Portfolio: https://sephta.github.io/ - personal portfolio